<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Minima</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Minima</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">minima.global</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Minima</string>
    <string name="menu_maxima">Maxima</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">MDS</string>

    <string name="menu_archive">Backup / Restore</string>
    <string name="menu_terminal">Terminal</string>

    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>

    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="minima_help">
Welcome to Minima\n
\n
The complete blockchain solution\n
\n
You now have access to a decentralised value and information transfer network unlike anything you have seen before\n
\n
An open application ecosystem known as the MDS - MiniDAPP System - allows you to interface easily with this new paradigm\n
\n
Value, Information and Application - everything you need to do anything you want\n
\n
We are still working hard to fit all the pieces together but we hope you enjoy this taste of Freedom\n
\n
The Minima Team</string>

    <string name="minima_backup">
        Making a backup of your Minima node is VERY important.\n
        \n
        On Minima you are the only one who looks after your coins.\n
        \n
        Currently - backups are only valid for 1-2 months.\n
        \n
        The files are about 500Kb.. so not very big.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_restore">
        You can easily restore from a backup.\n
        \n
        Once you have restored Minima will shutdown.\n
        \n
        When finished - please re-open Minima and your data will have been restored.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_archive">
        You can also resync from an Archive Node - but this should be as a LAST resort\n
        \n
        You can reset your chain to the latest tip or you can reset your NEW device to an old wallet\n
        \n
        When finished - please re-open Minima and your data will have been restored.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_archive_explain">
        Do NOT copy / paste your seed phrase here!\n
        \n
        The clipboard is insecure\n
        \n
        Either leave blank for a simple tip resync - if you are on the wrong chain - OR type each word individually and let the suggestions help you to reset your whole wallet..
    </string>

    <string name="minima_vaultlock">
        Encrypt your private keys with a password.\n
        \n
        You will not be able to send any coins or sign anything.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_vaultunlock">
        Decrypt your private keys with your password.\n
        \n
        You will be able to send coins and sign again.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_archive_chainsync">
        You can re-sync JUST the Minima blockchain.\n
        \n
        This will leave your wallet and keys untouched.\n
        \n
        You can do this if you find yourself on the wrong chain.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_archive_seedsync">
        As a last resort you can re-sync your entire wallet.\n
        \n
        If you lose your phone, and do not have a backup you can use JUST your seed phrase to do a complete Wallet re-sync.\n
        \n
        Your wallet and keys will be reset to the chosen seed phrase and all blocks re-downloaded.
    </string>

    <string name="minima_gdrive_backup_explanation_not_signed_in">Activate daily GDrive backups </string>
    <string name="minima_gdrive_backup_button_not_signed_in">Sign in to Google</string>

    <string name="minima_gdrive_backup_explanation_signed_in">GDrive User has activated daily backups\n\nThis happens automatically\n\nEmail:%s</string>
    <string name="minima_gdrive_backup_button_signed_in">Make GDrive backup Now</string>

    <string name="welcome_to_minima">Welcome to Minima</string>
    <string name="get_started">Start Minima</string>
    <string name="begin_setup">Begin Setup</string>
    <string name="onboarding_slide_description_one">Minima allows you to securely transact and communicate - without banks and without borders - with anyone else on the network.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_slide_description_two">The blockchain you are running ensures your transactions are secure and unalterable. Everyone running a Minima node shares this blockchain.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_slide_description_three">MiniDapps allow you to view information from the blockchain and interact with it, for example to send transactions.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_slide_description_four">Your node is unique to you, only YOU hold your data and funds.\n\nYou are independent and sovereign.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_slide_description_five">This Freedom comes with responsibility. Freedom is not Free. Make sure you make a backup regularly, at least once a month, and have a copy of your seed phrase.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_slide_description_six">You can do this.\n\nEmbrace it - and never look back.</string>

</resources>